#### Contact

bhartijaju2002@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

# Top Skills · See all

Adobe Illustrator · Creative
Content Creation · Graphic
Design · Social Media · Search
Engine Optimization (SEO) ·
Web Content Writing · Blogging
· Social Media Marketing · Video
Editing · Photography

Accomplishments · See all

6 Certifications · 2 Languages

Nagaur

## Summary

Through a multitude of experiences ranging from managing people and day-to-day operations for a non-profit to working as a digital marketer for startups. I found my life's calling in this field. Passionate about Management, I am pursuing MBA-International Marketing in my postgrad. My Graduation journey provided me with a lot of opportunities to upgrade myself as a human b...

Read more

### Experience

Blogger · Kraft-Obench - WFH Pods | Home Offices | Sound Insulated Work Pods

April 2022 - June 2022 (3 months)

Graphic Designer · enviNova Smartech

February 2022 - May 2022 (4 months)

Social Media Marketing Intern · ClearExam

June 2021 - August 2021 (3 months) · India

Content Writing Intern · The Site Traffic

June 2021 - July 2021 (2 months) · Jaipur, Rajasthan, India

#### Education

### JK LAKSHMIPAT UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Entrepreneurship/Entrepreneurial Studies  $\cdot$  (2019 - 2022)